semvironment.com 2008-06-24

# Privacy Policy | semvironment

### Privacy Policy

semvironment is committed to the privacy of guests visiting our Web site, our clients, and our clients’ program participants. We believe in loyalty and know that the basis of a loyal relationship is trust. You can trust that we will make every effort to keep your online and off-line information private and safe. The purpose of this policy is to ensure that visitors to our Web site understand what information semvironment gathers about Web site visitors and how it is used.

**Web Site Privacy**

semvironment gathers information on our Web site for the purpose of responding to visitors’ inquiries about our company. Our “Contact Us” form is provided for visitor inquiries/comments and can capture a number of personal information items, with all fields being voluntary.

We also use information captured in Web server log files to administer and improve our Web site. This information is used to monitor usage of the site, analyze trends, and make improvements to content and usability. IP addresses are used to track and analyze visitor traffic on our Web site, and gather broad demographic information. All information is anonymous, used in an aggregate format and is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

semvironment uses cookies only to enhance the functionality of our Web site and increase its usefulness to visitors.

semvironment is the sole owner and we will never sell, rent or share your information unless ordered by a court of law. All the information from our Web site is stored in a secure data center.

**E-mail/Anti-Spam Policy**

semvironment is strongly opposed to unsolicited commercial e-mail (SPAM). We use e-mail to communicate with parties requesting information from our company, with clients to whom we are providing services and individuals participating in the programs that we create for our clients. All of our e-mail communications are delivered in full compliance with requirements set forth in the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003. For more information on this act, please go to <http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/buspubs/canspam.htm>.

If you have questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact webmaster@semvironment.com.
